NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
{A Pure Betrayal
{A Fleeting Wish
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto! Grab on!
Okay, pull him up!
There, eh?!
Damn! Was it a clone?!
Over here!
Counterattack here it comes!
Rasengan go!
What...?!
You little...!
Yes!
Be careful, Naruto!
There are two others hiding!
Hey, there they are!
Kagero!
Let's retreat for now!
Hold it!
Th-They're totally quick
at running away!
Naruto, why're you spacing out?!
Where's Sakura?
Oh! Oh no!
Sakura!
Oh! Naruto...
Thank goodness!
You're okay, Sasame.
Yes... Sasame's okay.
Sasame's totally okay.
What're you mad about?
Let's take a break here.
Sakura... Who's the cute girl?
Okay! That's close enough...
What's the deal... Sakura?
Okay, don't come any closer!
Wh-What... I'm only interested
in adult women!
You must not misunderstand...!
Don't misunderstand!
It's not a misunderstanding.
It seems Sakura's finally figured out
Pervy Sage's true nature!
I told you to stop calling me
a "Pervy Sage"!
Then you're the Lewd Sage!
Both of you stop it! Sasame's scared!
— Okay.
Jeez...
This girl is Sasame...
She's a Ninja from
the Land of Rice Paddies...
A member of the Fuma Clan.
She had her cousin taken away
by Orochimaru
and was looking for his hideout.
Right. And the Ninja just now
were after Sasame
in order to protect the secret
of the hideout!
Oh... With the Fuma Clan, huh?
Huh?! You know?
I had contact with Ninja in the town
who'd left the Fuma Clan.
What! So you were actually doing
some serious investigating, Pervy Sage?!
I-I can't believe it...!
Well, you see when I went to
this nice-looking bar
it just turned out to be their hideout.
What! So after all you were just
hanging out with some girls, right?
You mustn't talk in a way that'll
lead to a misunderstanding!
Even Sakura who respects me will...
I've long since stopped respecting you!
I... I see...
Members of the Fuma Clan...?
Yeah. The boss was called Hanzaki
or something...
Hanzaki and the others are traitors
who abandoned the clan.
Oh...
Did those people do something?
They were after my travel money
so I taught them a lesson.
While at it I attempted to ask them about
Orochimaru's hideout...
but they didn't know anything.
I can show you the way to
Orochimaru's hideout.
For real?!
Yes...
All right!
Your wound hasn't healed yet.
Don't push yourself.
Yes... but...
This is the entrance to
the Village Hidden in Sound.
Orochimaru's hideout is deep
in those mountains...
I bet Sasuke is
somewhere in those mountains...
Okay at last!
Let's hurry!
Well, hold on...
Why?!
If we don't hurry night will fall before
we arrive at Orochimaru's hideout...
That's right!
Sasuke is just a stone's throw away!
Pervy Sage!
If we're going to save him
we should do it as soon as possible!
Why do we have to wait?!
Huh...?
What?
Gee...
Well... I'm hungry you see...
You know... All Shinobi must...
I can't fight if I'm hungry!
Up ahead will become full-blown
enemy territory.
We won't have time to
have relaxed meals so...
Okay, you guys eat too! Eat!
Mm, this is good...
You prepared this especially for us?
No. It seems the prettiest girl
in the bar fell to my charm you see.
She made these with tender loving care.
I'll go make some tea.
Oh... thanks...
Tastes pretty good.
Tea is ready.
Here you go!
Here you go.
Thanks...
Thank you Sasame...
Sasame, you should come here
and eat with us too.
Okay...
Pervy Sage... What's wrong...?!
Naruto...!
Sasame did it...
Since it's come to this, they're ours.
Your wound still hasn't healed.
Kagero, you wait here.
No mistake... They're Leaf Ninja.
If we take care of the Leaf pursuers...
Orochimaru-sama will surely acknowledge
the power of the Fuma Clan.
Yeah...
Let's come back with good news.
And with the heads of
the Leaf Ninja as souvenirs!
I finally found it!
At first I thought it was someone
from the Hidden Leaf Village.
But it's Sasame believe it or not...
Kamikiri, Jigumo, Kagero...
This is an odd reunion.
Where's Arashi?!
He wasn't with all you guys?!
Arashi is serving near Orochimaru-sama
and is spending his days training.
Can I see Arashi?!
If you're also going to work together
with us for Orochimaru-sama
I'm sure you'll be able to see him.
How'd it go?
You've done well.
With this I'll be able to see Arashi, right?
After we've finished them off!
Why?! Weren't we just supposed to
take them to Orochimaru-sama
for examination after capturing them?!
We only need the heads
for the examination.
No!
These people... For my sake...!
Move it!
— Wha...?!
— Huh?!
What?!
The Fuma numbing medicine
didn't work!
We knew about it all along
from the beginning!
Sakura!
Substitution...?!
I leave Sasame to you!
Leave her to me!
Sasame... Hang in there!
Why...? Why does Sasame have
to do something like this?!
No, it's not that she's doing it
against her will...!
It's something she wanted to do!
Liar!
It's true...
What...
What should I do to be able
to see Arashi again?
It's not a difficult thing.
You just have to put the lights out of those
who infiltrated the Land of Rice Paddies.
We have to kill them...?!
We'll take them back to Orochimaru-sama
for examination.
So we're not going to kill, right?
If we carry out that work
Orochimaru-sama will acknowledge us.
Hanzaki says that Arashi and everyone
are being tricked by Orochimaru.
He says that you'll just be used
and thrown away...
Hanzaki's just a traitor
who abandoned the village.
Will you believe what we say?
Or will you believe what a traitor says?
Orochimaru-sama will surely restore
our Fuma Clan...
Sasame, although you're still young
you're also one of the Fuma.
Assist in the restoration
of our Fuma Clan...
So you guys did trick Sasame!
It's all for the restoration
of the Fuma Clan!
You little!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Here I go!
Wha...!
U-Zu-Ma-Ki...!
Naruto Barrage!
This is bad...!
Rasengan!
This is for Sasame.
Prepare yourselves!
Naruto!
You're... from before?!
The Earth Style Jutsu user
in question, huh?
However, there's no point to using that
Art in this rocky area.
Indeed the Ant Lion appears from
inside the ground
and the spreading of its wings under
the sunlight is
but a momentary gleam.
That's when I die as Kagero!
Be careful!
What's this...?
Look! Naruto...
Wha...?!
U-Unbelievable!
You were a woman...?!
The clan will once again be
in a place lit by the sunlight...
Orochimaru-sama promised that...
I'll use this once-in-a-lifetime Art
if it's for the sake of that.
Kagero's Ninja Art: Ephemera!
Naruto! Come with me!
Naruto!
I-I feel like... I've seen this before...
It's Toad Mouth Trap Jutsu.
I summoned the extraordinarily
sturdy stomach of
the Mount Myoboku's
Iwajuku Giant Toad.
Stomach...?
Yikes!
It's melting...
If I didn't do this
we wouldn't have been able to
defend ourselves from her Chakra.
I believed... that the clan
would someday...
I believed in that.
Sh-She vanished.
I've got to hand it to her.
She probably put all of her life
on the line
and attempted to save her comrades...
It's unforgivable!
Those guys...
the Fuma Ninja...
Their feelings toward the clan
is the same as our feelings!
Manipulating the Fuma's desire
to restore their clan...
I'll kick Orochimaru's ass no matter what!
Wh-Where are we?
Kagero...!
You risked your life to save us?
You idiot...
Please...
Please use your Medical Ninjutsu
to save her.
Our comrade doesn't have
long to live!
Put your hands to your chests and think.
Think about what you weren't
able to accomplish... okay?
We risked our lives working for you...
to help you Orochimaru-sama.
In order to restore the Fuma Clan!
Please recognize our work!
You'll just have to atone for
your failure with your bodies.
Orochimaru-sama!
I'm sorry for the betrayal!
hitotsu hitotsu omoidaseba
when I recalled the parts one by one,
subete wakatteita kigashite ita no ni
I felt as though I had understood everything
iroaseta kotoba wa
faded words
boku no sugu soba ni oite atta
which I kept so close to me
kotae no denai yoru to
speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
hitokira no nukumori to
and this distant yearning for you
haruka kanata no akogare to
I live,
tada sore dake wo
simply repeating this cycle
kurikaeshi boku wa ikite iru
held in my two hands
kono ryoute ni kakaete iru mono
a droplet of time
toki no shizuku
softly clutching forgotten memories
sotto nigirishimete wasureta kioku
lost words
nakushita kotoba
I'll keep these thoughts...
kono omoi wa
That's Orochimaru's residence!
It really is just like him to construct
his residence underground.
Sasuke is somewhere inside
that residence right?
Sakura let's hurry!
Right!
Be careful!
First Avenue of hell is up ahead!
Will a devil appear
or will a snake appear?
Heh! I'm looking forward to it!
I'll kick the butts of the devil
and the snake.
And I'll save Sasuke and Arashi!
Next time:
"Terror! Orochimaru's Mansion."